Sir, Aka says he spotted a monster
ahead that looks like the King of Souls.
We found him, huh?
Everyone's depending on us, Boxxo.
Let's do our best!
Hello there!
How's it looking?
The King of Souls and some monsters
under his command are just ahead.
There are five corpse fiends, five undead,
eight skeleton fiends,
and four flame skulls.
There are 22 bodyguards in total.
Not impossible, but not easy either.
If the Vice Captain were here, we could
just wipe them all out with magic.
I mean, I could probably take down a
couple of them before they got too close.
We should whittle down their numbers
before we engage them head on.
Mr. Boxo?
Have you come up with a plan?
It looks like the device
that sprays out water.
I bet something probably comes out
of the tip if you pull the trigger.
Hello there!
Whoa, you were right!
Ugh, stuff stinks!
Is this mystery liquid
safe to touch? Hello there!
It feels greasy and it
kind of reminds me of oil.
I wonder if it'll burn.
It's incredibly volatile.
Are you suggesting we douse the
enemy in this flammable oil?
Hello there.
Okay, all we have to do is
follow the plan. Here it goes!
Now!
I'll remove just the bottle.
Then, we'll move in using the
barrier to keep out the flames,
heat, and carbon dioxide.
It'll be okay.
I can block any kind of magic.
You managed to defend against that?
I see.
That pale blue light must
be a barrier. Uh-huh!
Mm-ya!
Mommy!
Skeleton V!
Where did these reinforcements come from?
We can't count on the others for help.
You better go.
There's something suspicious
about that box on your back.
Beats me.
I don't know what you're talking about!
Oh, stones are ice! What?
You can withstand this?
Then I'll simply blow you
and that barrier away!
Huh, that was too easy.
What's going on?
Is she using magic to withstand the winds?
Nope, it's her blessing of might.
This is nothing!
It'll take more than some bad weather!
Forward! Don't stop!
Can't lose!
I see now.
It seems I've misunderstood
the source of your power.
But there's absolutely nothing you can do
before this battle or worth an expense!
Honor your baleful wales!
Hey!
That's no way!
Form change!
Thanks, Voxo!
Hello there!
Shores of Earth, close!
Curse, you girl!
I got it!
That was great, Shui!
That's not enough to stop me! Oh yeah?
Why don't you try this on for size then?
Voxo?
Yeah!
Oh!
I can't believe it!
That was amazing!
I gotta say, I didn't expect you to take
down the King of Souls so easily. Duh!
If Lamas can get her power under control,
she'd pretty much be unstoppable.
How dare you!
Who the hell do you people think I am?
Enough of that.
Figures an undead
doesn't know when to die.
You deserve to suffer a thousand
deaths for treading upon my greatness.
Yeah, that's rich coming
from a talking skeleton.
Give me one reason I shouldn't smash
you to bits and collect your coin.
You love my coin?
You think I'm a new stratum lord?
This is really bad! Get away!
Wait, what?
How come everything's gone black?
Points reduced by 500.
Is it over?
Guys, get up!
This is bad.
You're the first adventurers to
have survived my dark torrent.
I'll take back this arm of
the dead that clings to life.
It doesn't belong to you.
Not just anyone deserves to
use such a superior magic item.
Wouldn't you agree, old visitor
from another world? Hold up.
He knows who I am?
Who are you supposed to be?
My name has long been
forgotten by your kind.
Though I suppose I've been
referred to as the Netherlord.
So, this is the Stratum Lord's coin?
What an amusing bubble.
Why did you attack us like that?
Why do you ask?
What other reason does one need to hunt?
Didn't you yourself
come to this stratum to
kill the King of Souls
for your own benefit?
It's not the same!
Then please enlighten me.
What makes it somehow different?
Well, human...
How unfortunate.
That was a phantom.
No, Mishuel!
An attack from behind!
We were in the middle of a conversation.
Have you forgotten what matters?
Don't try to bite that thing head
on, it's too dangerous! Poxo! On it!
Oh, don't tell me that's all you've got!
How about this?
Now's our chance to get out of here!
Oh?
We've gotta go!
Time to leave!
You aren't going anywhere!
You're a troublesome one.
Kill me!
Despite everything, you
attack me from behind again!
Shui!
Don't touch them, you monster!
Lamas, get away!
Please, hurry!
Take the others and run!
Oh, what a treat.
Getting to see the human
spirit of self-sacrifice.
Very well.
Stop it!
Let you give me a treat!
You can't be gone.
You promised you'd always be there
to help me out, no matter what.
Everyone at the orphanage
is counting on you.
Get up. Please.
I'm begging you, open your eyes!
You can't be dead!
Cry all you want.
But they won't be waking up again.
Oh, no.
Llamas is totally out
of control at this rate.
You hurt too bad.
I know that, Boxxo.
There's no way I can hit him like this.
Hello there. But still,
if we can't figure out some way to stop
him, Everybody's going to die here!
You're right!
That's why I came up with a plan!
But if it doesn't work out, you could
potentially lose your life for nothing!
What's the matter?
Have you already given up?
I was hoping you would provide me with
a bit more entertainment, you bore!
Please block it!
How dreadfully prosaic.
Thanks for that, Boxo.
Hello there.
I know you'll come up with
a way to beat this creep.
And until then, I won't ever give up.
That's right.
She's counting on me.
I have to put my trust into her too.
Huh? Boxo?
You could even win a reward.
Oh, I see.
Have you already thought of a plan?
Hello there. Great!
Let's do this, then.
It appears you've finished saying
your final goodbyes to each other.
Fear not, I am not a cruel being.
I will reunite you with your
dearly-deported friends soon enough,
using my most powerful
technique! It's time!
For the first step, I'll use my
barrier to eject Lamas at full power!
Here we go! No!
Now for step two.
I'll shoot the balloons out.
Absurd.
To think you were able to
shatter the arm of the dead.
I look forward to seeing how
your group develops further.
I'll be waiting for you
to come and find me.
Yulemi, wake up!
You promised you'd help me.
You can't make good on your promise if
you die and leave me all alone, right?
Please, open your eyes.
Yulemi, Shui, there's still
so much we have to do.
This can't be the end.
That son of a bitch!
Shui! Shui!
I won't let you go!
Nobody in the Menagerie of
Bulls is allowed to die!
What do we do, Captain?
Don't just sit there!
Didn't the association teach you
what to do in these situations?
Right.
Is that a cardiac massage?
Hold on, I think I've
got something for this.
I do!
Huh?
For Boxer to change forms all of a sudden,
that must mean he's got
an item up his sleeve.
I agree, but I've never
seen this form before.
Yeah, that tracks.
Even in my old world, the average person
probably wouldn't know how to use an AED.
How can I expect the people of
this world to understand it?
But I don't have time to explain!
I don't care how many points this costs!
Huh? It's floating!
Are you saying this'll save them?
Hello there!
Expose the patient's chest and retrieve
the square bag from underneath the lid.
Afterwards, tear open the
bag and remove the pads.
Sure, on it!
Now for the hard part.
In order to maximize the
chance that this'll work,
I'll increase my dexterity
with the rest of my points!
I'm finished, Boxo! Is this good?
Hello there. Right.
First off...
Please do not touch the patient.
Now recording EKG.
Scan complete. Reading measurements.
Electric shock is required.
Move away from the body.
This has to work!
Electric shock has been performed.
Begin manual cardiac massage immediately.
Okay.
Oh no.
I was too late.
If only I had thought of this sooner.
Yulami, why aren't you waking up?
Voxo gave us a special item
to help bring you back.
So please open your eyes. Yulami!
Lamas?
What happened?
Yulami!
Voxo, come on, Jusui!
Hello there!
Captain?
What's going on?
Did we win?
Don't need to be careful, you dummy!
Hold on!
That's so hard, I can't breathe!
Thank goodness they're alright!
Seems the people here are
sturdier than I thought.
I'm sorry for being so
useless during the fight.
You put your trust in me, and when it
really counted, I wasn't able to save you.
No need to apologize.
I talked a big game, but in the end,
I wasn't able to do anything either.
Yes, I'm here.
That was the Netherlord, huh?
He's seriously bad news.
We have to let Director Bear
know as soon as possible.
He was truly a monstrous opponent.
If we were to fight him again, I'm not
sure I'd be able to protect everyone.
Several days later,
after Hulemy and Shui had fully recovered,
we made our way back to
the Clearflow Lake Stratum.
As soon as we arrived,
the first thing we did was report
the incident to Director Bear.
I see.
And you're sure he was the Netherlord?
Sounds like you've heard of him before.
Indeed.
Though I don't know much
since I've only read his
name in passing while
perusing some old records.
But I suspect he's a general
serving the Demon Lord.
Hold on.
You're saying there's someone
even stronger than him?
In light of this new information,
I'll be requesting an emergency meeting
with the directors of each stratum.
You've done well.
I want you to get plenty of rest in
case anything unexpected happens.
Right.
Hey, missus! I'm back!
Oh, Lamas!
I was worried.
Please tell me you're all right.
Yep.
You're finally back!
Oh. Huh.
Why do I feel like I've
seen this scene before?
Are you okay?
You're not hurt anywhere, are you?
Calm down.
I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
I heard you ran into an enemy that
was stronger than a stratum lord,
and I was so worried I
couldn't even sleep a wink.
Don't worry, Munami. I'm home.
Apparently,
the story about us fighting
the nether lord had already
started spreading throughout
the village like wildfire.
We heard about what happened, Boxo.
It's a good thing you were there,
otherwise things could have been bad.
Too bad.
Don't be modest now.
You drove off a monster
stronger than a stratum
lord and saved Hulemy and
Shui while you were at it.
After everything you've done for us,
it's safe to say you're an irreplaceable
part of this village, Boxo.
It's really nice to
hear that kind of stuff.
But still...
Tale of your heroism has
spread far and wide, Mr. Boxo.
Hearing of it has only strengthened
my desire to bring you into my home.
Unfortunately, until that day comes,
you'll just have to put up
with living with Mommies!
Huh?
What was that about? Who knows?
Why are there so many
people in this village?
Mr. Mishel!
Yes! Who is...
Oh, it's you guys.
Did you need something from me?
We were wondering if you had
any other plans after this.
What?
We're going after the Nether Lord.
But to be honest, he's
so strong, it's scary.
Please keep fighting by our sides.
We can't do it without you.
I don't know how much use I'd be.
He defeated me handily.
Mr. Mishel? That's why.
I swear upon my blade.
Next time, I won't lose.
I promise from this day forth, I won't
allow any of my comrades to be hurt again.
Hooray!
By the way,
Director Bear said he was going to summon
expert hunters from each
of the other strata.
Like 40 or 50 people, right?
More than that, I heard him throw
around numbers in the hundreds.
If we really push, we could
probably recruit over a thousand.
There's no way we could lose, right, Mr.
Mishel?
But of course.
What's on your mind, Captain?
Are you okay?
I'm trying to figure out exactly what
we're hoping to achieve out here.
What?
I've always thought that as long as
I'm working towards getting my wish,
it'd be all right if I
dropped dead somewhere.
But now,
I've been thinking,
what gives me the right to put the lives
of my people at risk to achieve some goal,
one that might not even be possible?
It's not like that.
I never would have imagined hearing
such spineless words out of you.
That's right.
Also, that serious look
doesn't match you at all.
You guys.
We knew the risks when we joined
up with the Menagerie of Fools.
Don't think for even a second
that you have to coddle us.
See, Captain?
All you have to do is keep moving forward.
You can leave the rear to us.
We believe in you, so
keep your head up, okay?
They're right, you know.
I couldn't have said it better myself.
I get it already, so enough
with all the sappy speeches.
All right, then.
We're heading out tomorrow.
Akka, Shiro, gather up rations
and supplies for 30 days.
She'll be getting a tab, too.
Huh?
What do you mean, 30 days?
And you want us to pay?
Speaking of, Captain, I believe you
still owe us our wages for this month.
One morning,
Lamas put me on her back and left the
village without saying where we were going.
We walked along in silence.
Hmm.
I wonder where she's taking me.
Here we are, Boxo.
Hold on.
Do you recognize this place?
This is the exact spot you
and I first met each other.
Hello there!
Also, this is where you first saved me.
I still remember it.
Lamas...
So many things have happened
since I got to know you.
Lots of it was dangerous.
are scary.
But no matter what
happened on our adventures,
you always helped out and you
made sure everyone was safe.
You're wrong, Lamas.
We've just been lucky up to this point.
Our last battle made that
painfully obvious. Voxo,
something tells me that
you're blaming yourself
for what happened in the
Dead's Lament stratum.
But that's not true.
It's not your fault.
In fact, the only reason I was
unharmed was because you were there.
If it weren't for you,
we wouldn't have been able to save
Hulemy and Shui and they would have died.
So that's why.
You shouldn't feel down on yourself, okay?
You did nothing wrong.
Lamas,
it's amazing how much empathy you can show
towards a simple vending machine like me.
Huh, and here we were thinking
you might need some cheering up.
Looks like Lamas already has it covered.
Huh?
Yolami, Shui, how'd you find us?
How do you think?
We followed you after we heard you left
the village with Boxxo on your back.
Oh, dang.
And besides, we still haven't
thanked him for saving us.
Yep, that's right.
Wait, hold on a sec.
Back off!
I mean, what the heck are
you two doing to Boxxo?
We're just showing him our gratitude.
After all, if it weren't for
him, we'd be in the afterlife.
Come to think of it, you owe
Boxo a lot, too, don't you?
You could thank him
now and then, you know.
Well, thank him?
I guess it's only fair if
I give him a reward, too.
Plus, Mom would always remind me
it's polite to give proper thanks.
It's happening.
I can't do it, Boxo.
I'm so sorry.
I'm about to die from
embarrassment, Olive.
It's stalling. Just go.
Hey!
You jerks!
You finally did it!
You came for this! Come here!
Being reborn as a vending
machine to wander the
dungeon in another world
is a ridiculous premise.
But after everything I've been through
and meeting a bunch of new people,
I think I'd like to keep
living this kind of life.